{
    "id": "aafbdecc25a4478999c5448761e87811",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Take the umbrella with you in case it ........................",
            "description": "In subordinate clauses we often use a present tense to refer to future.",
            "answers": [
                "will rain",
                "is raining",
                "rains"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The first time I ............................. there was last year.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to simply state when something happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "have gone",
                "had gone",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the village where I was ..........................",
            "description": "Where means the same as in which.",
            "answers": [
                "born",
                "born in",
                "born at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ............................... a couple of months ago.",
            "description": "We cannot use the present perfect tense with a past time expression.",
            "answers": [
                "had got married",
                "has got married",
                "got married"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the man whom we met ..........................",
            "description": "The relative pronoun serves as the subject or object of the relative clause. Hence we do not need another subject or object in the relative clause.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "him there",
                "there"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have warned you a ............................. not to do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hundred times",
                "hundreds times",
                "hundred of times"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think ................................ she is interested in coming.",
            "description": "That can introduce a noun clause. The conjunction so..that is mainly used to indicate the purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "as",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ............................. hair.",
            "description": "Hair is uncountable. It cannot be used with the article a.",
            "answers": [
                "long",
                "a long",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... the cold she insisted on going out.",
            "description": "Despite or in spite of is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Despite of",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ she arrives, give her this message.",
            "description": "Before a clause we use in case.",
            "answers": [
                "In case",
                "In case of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven't seen him since .............................",
            "description": "There is no preposition or article before expressions like last week.",
            "answers": [
                "last week",
                "the last week",
                "in the last week"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................ school at the age of twelve.",
            "description": "We cannot use the present perfect tense with time expressions referring to the past.",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "had left",
                "has left"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}